http://www.advertisersprinting.com/privacy-policy/

Our Privacy Policy
We respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have adopted this privacy policy. This privacy policy lets you know how your personal information is processed and explains our data collection and use practices. “Advertisers Printing” includes all web pages, newsletters, and opt-in announcement lists owned and operated by us. By accessing our website, you are consenting to the information collection and use practices described in this privacy policy. We promise that we will use your personal information only in ways that are compatible with this privacy policy as follows:
What information are you collecting and how are you collecting it?
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers, that serve as that computer’s “Internet Protocol” IP address. When a visitor requests a page from any website within Advertisers Printing, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor’s domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you other than the IP address from which you have accessed our websites. We use this information to examine our traffic in aggregate, and to investigate misuse of the our network, its users, or to cooperate with law enforcement. We do not collect and evaluate this information for specific individuals. Our web servers do not automatically record e-mail addresses of the visitors.
What personal information do you collect?
Wherever we collect personal information, we make an effort to include a link to this privacy policy. We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. The personal information we collect may include your name, title, company or organization name, e-mail address, phone number, work or home address, information about your job function, and information about your company. We may request your e-mail address or mailing address for the purposes of conducting a contest or to provide additional services (for example, subscriptions to announcement lists or information about conferences and trade shows). Participation in contests or other promotions at Advertisers Printing is completely voluntary and you have a choice whether or not to disclose personal information.We may from time to time send e-mail announcing new products and services. If you choose to supply your postal address in an online form, you may receive postal mailings from us and our third party affiliates.We maintain a strict “No-Spam” policy that means that we do not sell, rent, or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third-party, without your consent or as permitted by this privacy policy.Your consent to this agreement by using the Advertisers Printing, you consent to the collection and use of information by us as specified above. We reserve the right to modify this privacy policy. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.Please send any questions about our privacy policy to : wf@advprinting.com.Most recently updated June, 2015.
Explore
Menu
Home
What We Do
What We Do
How We Do It
Our Business Philosophy
Our History
1229 S. Vandeventer Ave.St. Louis, MO 63110Phone: (314) 652-9924Fax: (314) 652-9049
Facebook-f
Twitter
Linkedin-in
Privacy Policy | Terms of Use © 2020, The Advertisers Printing Company. All Rights Reserved.
